in my very first video exact little big pharma introversion itinerary no one
在我的第一个视频中，几乎没有什么大药房的内向行程了
direction the couples with go back then my fingers more clear to mean a like many
方向夫妇一起回去，然后我的手指更清晰，意味着很多
or you poor stoicism enthusiastic lately and
还是您最近的热情高涨，
wonder tip fresh connection between my fascination for this ancient philosophy
我对这个古老哲学的迷恋之间有新的联系
and my introverted the staff eighty years' war on fire
我向员工发动了八十年的交火
[Music]
[音乐]
in a world that celebrates extra virgin
在一个庆祝处女的世界里
bean an introvert it is always easy the strands of introvert soft and over succeeds
内向的人总是容易的，内向的人柔和而成功
see in the kerry's brand chatterbox and rising toe up the stairs
在凯利（Kerry）的品牌chatterbox中看到，然后从脚尖爬上楼梯
the stump silent tips some times even first-rate him
树桩无声提示有时甚至一流
you to the constant lack of recognition what what introverted sunmaster set is
您一直缺乏认识，内向的太阳大师套装是什么
spending time hello and was them best way to utilize of
花费时间你好，这是他们利用的最佳方法
solitude and meursinge cells and philosophy
孤独与被抚养的细胞与哲学
looking at stork exercises to matter if it's to visualize the neck at Marcus
看鹳运动对在马库斯看脖子是否重要
aurelius journaling or the more i did how you're going to by having that most
aurelius日记，或者更多，我做了那么多您打算如何做
of them a solitary practices in which i actually the touch of even van life and
他们中的一种孤立的做法，实际上我甚至触及了面包车的生活，
the outcomes of the how not from growth or introspection to execute the
如何不从增长或内省执行结果
exercises and most introverts tent of stream introspective capabilities
练习和最内向的流内省能力
so win it comes to the practical sense of this stoicism
所以赢了，这就是这种坚忍的实践意义
and introversion go well together some introvert however at the tendency to
和性格内向相处得很好，但是有内向的倾向
level agreements and even a beautiful world that just can't keep
级别协议，甚至是一个无法维持的美丽世界
its mouth shut eye the middle to the end quite prone to this myself he can
它的嘴闭上了眼睛，直到中间到最后，我自己很容易做到这一点，他可以
spend with hotel king 2 single person and be perfectly fine
与酒店国王2单人同行并度过完美时光
like many introverts he doesn't my own time to recharge my berry he love
像许多性格内向的人一样，他没有自己的时间给我爱的浆果充电
relaxing my mind side effects loon in nature and the idea of ​​excluding myself
放松我的思想副作用大自然中的懒人和排除自己的想法
on society even if it's just temporary of te
即使只是暂时的
scratch smite however marcus aurelius things that would only source literally
从头开始就sm一息，但只能从字面上寻找来源
for the health to find and for something eset and a quote people secret reach
为了寻找健康，为了某种东西和引述人们秘密接触
for them even in the countryside but the seashore in the hills and you to
对于他们来说，即使是在乡村，但在山坡上的海边，
major head to long before above all health what this is all together and
最重要的是，首先要很健康
philosophical when is possible for you to reach
在可能的情况下达到目标
into your self when from you place for no work and
当您离开工作场所时进入自己的自我
one retreat into great piece of freedom from care
撤退到极大的自由照顾
than how many us die socially and quote
比我们有多少人在社交上死亡和报价
violating there even of the world who might actually i want to practice of
甚至在世界上都违反了我可能实际上想练习的
power of science in the fog of people many people 12
在许多人中雾中的科学力量12
just for the site of interpreters and c and let of nothing about things they don't know
仅用于口译员和c的站点，对于他们不知道的事情一无所获
anything about so tender in a cream is full of blubber
奶油里这么嫩的任何东西都充满了润滑脂
there a greater soon than the ability to be silent epictetus
比沉默沉默的能力要快得多
tellson's how it's done and close the foremost bart silent
泰森的做法和关闭最重要的巴特无声
of speak merely what is necessary and in a few words you may however and joy
只是说什么是必要的，用几句话来说，您可能会感到高兴
kill sparingly into this course some times location goals for it but not own
偶尔杀死这门课程，有时为其定位目标，但不拥有目标
any or the comments object half gladiator 'or or graces or eft
任何或评论对象为半角斗士'或或恩典或eft
laure campion of east the trapdoor topics of
东部劳伦·坎皮（Laure Campion）的活板门主题
conversation 'what principally that or one like side to blame
对话”，这主要是指责还是指责相似的一面
traveling to i come persons if you were able
如果可以的话，来我这里旅行
them by there also converse brin excess or your company to top subject but if
他们在那里也可以逆转布林过多或贵公司成为最重要的话题，但是如果
you have to be rangers should be silent and quote shouldn't isolate
你必须是护林员，应该保持沉默，不要孤立地引用
Philosophers even replied that how student hangout with the room company
哲学家甚至回答说，学生如何与客房公司进行环聊
lawyer and engage a bird and which like en gossip for example
律师和一只鸟，例如像恩八卦
this means that we might want to be selective content choice of friends
这意味着我们可能希望成为朋友的选择性内容选择
android negative people stand like that
android负面人物像那样站立
else need decent company available it's better to be alone picas in one
否则需要一家像样的公司，最好是一个人陪伴异国情调的人
lonis by plenty of a virtual things to do like working on thinks that would
lonis从事许多虚拟工作，例如在工作上认为这会
use guys offering or maybe les ambitious stay no way from thinks that
使用家伙提供或也许野心勃勃的住宿，从没有办法认为
other harmful introverts and provide silent listeners
其他有害的性格内向者，并提供沉默的听众
of you manage and the ones who then to think and reflect a bit more om live
你们中的一些人，然后思考并反思更多生活的人
events there are additional counterparts and then use of this is that we over
事件中还有其他对应对象，然后使用它，我们结束了
think and perhaps people's analyzer on an instrument to the point who images
思考，也许人们的分析仪在仪器上成像谁
on a site that stick wisdom can count rotec so when prompted to control c or
在坚持智慧的网站上可以算出rotec，因此当系统提示您控制c或
mistake intouchables kind or rationality like that
像这样的错误
reflective capacities be-commerce a tail about nmi
反射能力在商务方面落后于nmi
this way we can for example deal with difficult people in their heads we would
这样，例如，我们可以与头脑中的困难人士打交道，我们会
also an award here is a quote from marcus aurelius to
这里也有一个奖项是马库斯·奥雷留斯（Marcus aurelius）对
show you what am i wanna know problem view or hate you or people voice simple
向您展示我想知道问题的观点，还是讨厌您或别人的声音简单
criticisms go to their souls penetrate insight and
批评深入人心，洞察力和
see what sort of people there you will realize de theres no need to be reckoned
看看那里有什么样的人，你会意识到没有必要
with anxiety de they shoot hold any party kroop ring
带着焦虑的心情，他们开枪举行任何聚会
in about you and quote so dearly miss a lot of stoicism
在关于您的报价中，非常想念很多坚忍的人
suitable philosophy for introverts or the one you consider yourself
适合性格内向的人或您认为自己适合的人
introverted i am disturbing please let me know in the comment section
性格内向，我在打扰，请在评论部分告诉我
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
[Music]
[音乐]